dollskill.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Dolls Kill

  * **ALL ABOUT YOU BB**  
Your data will only be used to better your experience and fulfill our contract with you
  * **WE GOT YOUR BACK**  
We’ll protect your data like it’s our own
  * **NO BS**  
We’ll tell it to you straight in language that’s easy to understand
  * **FULL CONTROL**  
Your data, your preferences – you control what and how you hear from us
  * **AS NEEDED**  
Your info wont just sit around – if we don’t need it we’ll delete it

We respect your right to privacy at Dolls Kill! It’s important to us that you know how we collect and use your data, and that you know that your data will only be used to provide you with a better shopping experience

Most of the information you provide to us happens when you’re engaging with our brand. This information may include information that you volunteer when browsing the site, purchasing or registering for an account – like your name, email address, shipping address, billing address, credit card info – or information that is collect automatically through cookies and third-party tools when you interact with our digital assets – including visit history, purchase history, wishlisted items, IP address, date logs, and browser/device information.

We collect only the information necessary for us to provide you with a relevant, personalized and optimized shopping experience with us.

The tables below describe what we collect, why we collect it and how you can control it.

**Name and Contact Details**  
**How we use it** | **Why we use it** | **How to control it**  
---|---|---  
Deliver purchases to you | So you can get your order | Update information and preferences in your Account Dashboard; or email [contact@dollskill.com](mailto:contact@dollskill.com)  
Send order or customer service updates | To track your order or address a service issue  
To enable you to log into your account | So you have a place on Dolls Kill to manage your orders, wishlist and account info  
Send brand or marketing messages | To keep you up to date on the latest arrivals, deals, and exclusives | Click the unsubscribe link in any message; or email [contact@dollskill.com](mailto:contact@dollskill.com) to prevent physical mail  
  
**Payment Info**  
**How we use it** | **Why we use it** | **How to control it**  
---|---|---  
Take payment  | We’ve got to charge you before we send your goodiez | Visit Checkout and edit your Payment Info  
Fraud prevention and detection | To protect you or us against fraud  
  
**Purchase, Order, Wishlist and Browse History**  
**How we use it** | **Why we use it** | **How to control it**  
---|---|---  
Maintain your shopping session | So you can track the things you wishlist and add to cart  | Ask us to delete your data or choose not to shop with us :(  
Provide customer service, support and handle returns | We need your history to serve you better  
Show you stuff you’ll like | To make sure we’re giving you what you want  
  
**Cookie Data**  
**How we use it** | **Why we use it** | **How to control it**  
---|---|---  
Improve user-friendliness and functionality | To make sure you’re getting the best shopping experience | Delete and disable your cookies  
Protect our website | To prevent fraud against you and us  
  
For a more detailed look at what we collect, peep the section below:

Dolls Kill will use your contact info (email address, phone number, billing and/or shipping address) to let you create and maintain an account on Dolls Kill, process, deliver or return goodiez you purchase, contact you regarding the status of your order or reach you if there’s an issue. Dolls Kill will use your email address, gender, birthday or personal information you provide to us to let you know about our sik new items, dope dealz and special sales. You can always opt out by clicking the unsubscribe link included in the message.

If you decide to purchase from us, we’ll take your payment information in the form of Credit Card, PayPal or other form of payment. We’ll use the card, and address information to process your transaction via third-party payment processors. Through partners we may securely save these details for future use, tied to your account, for your convenience. No one can see or copy your protected payment deets.

There are times where we use other kinds of data to improve the quality of our services and provide you with the most personalized and relevant experiences. This may include using geo-targeted data like IP address to customize products/services to your location; using your purchase history and observed preferences to serve you other sik items or dealz you might like; monitoring trends/usage/activities to make sure our site is working as it should; protecting you against fraudulent or unauthorized transactions; or addressing customer service issues you may have via site chat or social media.

Dolls Kill does utilize "cookies" to help recognize you as a repeat visitor and to track traffic patterns on our site. We use this info to improve the user-friendliness and functionality of our site.

Dolls Kill will not sell your name or personal information without your permission. But we do sometimes need to share your information with carefully selected third-party services in order to provide you with relevant experiences. Each of these tools are vetted to assure they are as protective of your data as we are.

We use your card and address information to process transactions via third-party payment processors. We don’t store your credit card information, but our payment partners may to make your future purchases easier and faster.

If you use third-party services, such as Facebook, to log into your account, information must be shared with the partner for this to work. It helps you log in faster in the future and saves you time from remembering your password. 

Dolls Kill does reserve the right to participate in cooperative database services. These services help us to direct print catalogs, mailings, digital ads, and other marketing initiative to appropriate purchasers and website visitors. 

Name and mailings addresses may be shared between participating parties in the cooperative database services, but no credit card information or other sensitive personal information is ever provided to the cooperative. 

If we need to share personal information with third parties to perform services on our behalf, then the third party’s access, use and disclosure of the personal data must also comply with EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield frameworks. That ensures that companies have a standard for protecting and processing your data.

You’ve got a bunch of rights relating to your personal information. These include:

  * The right to be informed about how your info is being used (like this notice!)
  * The right to access the personal info we hold about you
  * The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal info we hold about you
  * The right to request that we purge, stop processing or stop collecting your data in select circumstances
  * The right to stop direct marketing messages by opting out
  * The right to request that we transfer your data either to you or another service provider
  * The right to complain to your data protection regulator — in the UK, the Information Commissioner’s Office

Don’t forget BB - If you want to exercise your rights, have a complaint to make, or just have a question for us - get in touch at [contact@dollskill.com](mailto:contact@dollskill.com)

We keep your deets on file for as long as you have an account with us, as long as it is needed to provide our services to you or as long as is required to maintain support related activities. In some cases we may hold information after you have closed your account if it is necessary to meet certain legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud or abuse or enforce terms and conditions.

You have full control over your deets. You can always choose not to provide certain information, though some data may be required to make a purchase or take advantage of certain features. 

You have the right to access personal data we hold about you and to ask that this data be corrected. You can either do this by logging into and updating the information in your account or by contacting customer service.

In either case, you can ask that we erase or restrict the data we are processing; or you can require that we provide you with your personal data in a portable form for transmission to another service. 

If you have questions regarding your data protection, please contact our data protection officer (DPO) at [dataprotection@dollskill.com](mailto:dataprotection@dollskill.com).

All content on this site, including, but not limited to: informational content, graphic images, and program code such as html and javascript are the copyrighted material of Dolls Kill, and may not be reproduced in any manner without the expressed written consent of Dolls Kill. All prices listed are accurate to the best of our ability. In the rare case an item is mislisted, Dolls Kill reserves the right to refuse to sell the item at the listed price. Please note that upon placing an order, a receipt is automatically mailed confirming the purchase intent. This receipt does not constitute a contract, and orders may be canceled at any time due to insufficient stock, inability to authorize a credit card, suspicion of fraudulent intent, discovery of an incorrect item price, or any other reason as we see fit. Please further note that Dolls Kill shall have the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not your credit card has been charged. If your credit card has already been charged and your order is canceled, Dolls Kill shall issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the incorrect price.
